/*
 * Script for index.html
 * requires scripts.js
 */

const supernatural = {
  trivia: [
    {
      question: 'What woman did Dean go live with when Sam went to hell?',
      answers: {
        2: 'Lisa',
        3: 'Cassie',
        4: 'Ruby',
        1: 'Bella'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first creature you see the Colt kill?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Vampire',
        2: 'Werewolf',
        3: 'Demon',
        4: 'Ghoul'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which supernatural being can be identified easiest through a CCTV camera?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Shapeshifter',
        2: 'Vampire',
        3: 'Ghost',
        4: 'Wendigo'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many years older than Sam is Dean?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Four',
        2: 'Three',
        3: 'Five',
        4: 'Two'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the demon that killed Mary and Jess?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Azazel',
        2: 'Crowley',
        3: 'Alistair',
        4: 'Meg'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question:
        'The Archangel Gabriel was originally introduced under a different persona, but by what name was the trickster officially known?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Loki',
        2: 'Lilith',
        3: 'Papa Legba',
        4: 'Coyote'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who brought Castiel back from Purgatory?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Naomi',
        2: 'Zachariah',
        3: 'God',
        4: 'Michael'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the episode "The Benders", what was killing people?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Humans',
        2: 'Vampires',
        3: 'Rawheads',
        4: 'Reapers'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who says this in "Yellow Fever"? "I\'ll man the flashlight!"',
      answers: {
        1: 'Dean',
        2: 'Sam',
        3: 'Cas',
        4: 'Bobby'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question:
        'What was the name of Sam\'s girlfriend that died in the "Pilot" episode?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Jess',
        2: 'Ruby',
        3: 'Meg',
        4: 'Cassie'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    }
  ]
};
